- Dearly beloved...
- Okay.
we are gathered here today to
join Paul Duerson
and Sofia Minor
in holy matrimony.
Do you take Paul to be
your lawfully-wedded husband?
I do.
I hate it when
they show the ending first.
But I just couldn't
help myself.
You may kiss the bride.
Okay guys,
that's enough.
Back to the beginning.
So, what do you think?
It was my dad's.
Fits perfect, huh?
How was the tour?
Saw you guys in San Francisco.
Whoa-ho! Nice.
Don't do this. Just go.
William...
Tonight is the night.
I'm proposing.
I told you...
the next time you came around,
I was calling the police.
You're killing me.
We have to talk with you
about something.
I didn't want to do this.
Who?
Me and Sofia.
You know, my girlfriend?
She's not your girlfriend.
Okay, listen.
I know you're a lonely guy.
Because your wife died.
And that's why Sofia does
those puzzles with you.
She does them with you
because she feels bad
that your wife
died of stomach cancer,
and you have no one
to do puzzles with anymore.
How do you know
about the puzzles?
- Is she here?
- No.
Oh... oh, I can wait.
It's not a problem.
- No, no, no.
- No, it's really not...
Listen, I really don't want
to have to call the cops,
man, okay?
Just leave. Now.
You don't have to call them.
You don't have to.
You know, I could just
sit right... right in there.
Yeah.
- Okay.
High five.
Give it to me. I need it.
I need it.
Okay, Paul.
You got big hands.
Bye.
Oh, fuck. Go!
Goddammit.
Hey. Hey.
Why are you acting this way?
Take it easy.
Don't be mad at me, Ladybug.
I'm not mad at you.
You're confused.
We've been through this before.
You don't know Sofia.
You're wrong.
You are wrong.
Okay, you know her.
- Give me the knife.
- You.
What?
You're Sofia.
Don't you... Don't!
Look, I'm unarmed.
Let me help.
Say you're Sofia.
- Okay, I'm Sofia.
- And you love me.
I'm Sofia, and I love you.
Now, give me the knife, Paul.
Stay there.
Yeah. Oh, my god.
Here it is.
I have a ring.
It's really nice of you.
Will you marry me?
I don't know what to...
to say.
Put it on.
It's perfect.
Give me the knife, Paul.
♪ I am broken
My heart has spoken ♪
♪ You are broken, too ♪
♪ I'm afraid I'm depraved ♪
♪ But no one's depraved
Like you ♪
I freaking love that song.
I love it.
The wedding is going to be
at the Cassowary Tabernacle.
JH is my best man.
Pastor Tim Lutzner
is gonna perform the ceremony.
And... and, and...
I got this dagger.
Not this one.
It's a Rajput ceremonial
wedding dagger.
It's in Customs now,
but wait
until you see this thing.
I mean... we're gonna
look amazing up there.
I mean, for that alone.
What do you think?
You're pretty stone- faced
right now.
Okay, let's do it.
Really?
- You love me?
- Yes. I love you. Now...
now, please
just give me the knife.
Hmm.
Who should we tell first?
My family or yours?
♪ I used to be a lunatic
From the gracious days ♪
♪ I used to feel woebegone ♪
♪ And so restless nights ♪
♪ My aching heart would bleed ♪
♪ For you to see ♪
♪ Oh, but now ♪
♪ I don't find myself
bouncing home ♪
♪ Whistling buttonhole tunes
to make me cry ♪
Okay, um... I'm ready.
Ready for my interview.
Who is DeVante Rhodes?
Ah. Well...
he's the best point guard
in the game of basketball.
So he's hot.
Is that why you had your people
call me yesterday?
No. I don't even know
what a point guard does.
What else he say?
He said you were a trailblazer.
And I was like, "In what?"
I- I was traded
to the Nuggets.
That's a really silly name
for a basketball team.
Okay, so you called me up
to make fun of me?
Well, you seemed... like fun.
And I like to have fun.
Is that why you wrote that song?
What song?
I kind of like that one.
It's your turn.
You're up.
- All right.
- Move it.
What's your favorite
song of mine?
I told you.
"Girls Just Want to Have Fun."
That's Cyndi Lauper.
You're confusing
your white singers.
It's embarrassing.
Oh, uh... "Like a Prayer."
Do I look like Madonna?
A little. Actually.
Sofia?
It's Kaylor.
Your assistant?
I know who you are,
Kaylor. What's up?
William's here.
Who's, uh... who's William?
He goes by Bell.
That doesn't
answer my question.
I'll be down in a sec.
Does he seem okay to you?
What do you mean?
You know, is he healthy,
mentally?
Do you mean, like, twitchy?
He seems fine.
Are you twitchy?
Hey, Sof.
Hey!
Hmm.
- How's Abby?
- Oh, she's good. Thank you.
That's Rhodes.
- The Blazer?
- He's a Nugget now.
Come on, I wanna
show you something.
Have you met Waylon
up at the front booth?
His wife makes the best chili.
What the fuck?
Love it.
Ta- da!
Would you look at that.
Took me every bit
of the six months
- you were gone, too.
- Mm
Wow. Six months...
for this puzzle.
Shut up.
And here is our next challen...
You said I could choose.
There's a piece missing.
Yeah, I know.
It's driving me nuts.
I looked everywhere for it.
♪ Dear, I fear
We're facing a problem ♪
♪ You love me no longer ♪
♪ I know and ♪
♪ Maybe there is nothing
That I can do ♪
♪ To make you do ♪
♪ Mama tells me
I shouldn't bother ♪
♪ That I ought just stick
To another man... ♪
Sorry I'm late.
I figured I'd get
the silent treatment.
Came with reinforcements.
Here. You left it up here.
Not supposed to
have Coke this late.
Says who?
You.
Well...
I won't tell if you don't.
You ready?
Let's see.
You're upset because the Pirates
lost their third straight today.
That was a terrible game,
but that's not why I'm mad.
Drink.
Hmm. Okay.
Is it because
I'm going back to work?
And you were really
looking forward
to spending more time
with me this summer?
You're not that cool.
You're afraid
I could get hurt again.
I just hate
the whole idea of a bodyguard.
It's like saying your life
is less important than hers.
He called again today.
- Who?
- You know who.
Next time he does,
hang up and call me.
He just seemed confused.
My dearest JH,
by the time you're
reading this,
the best day of my life,
and therefore yours,
will be fast approaching.
So, by now, you should have
already picked up
my parcel
from the post office.
You wrote down
the lock combination
when we last spoke
so you should be able to
let yourself in.
I don't want to put too much
in writing because...
spies.
But I trust you're prepared
and remember the plan.
Oh, and please remember
to bring your eyepatch.
I love you so much, JH.
Sofia and I
could not be happier
that you're joining us
on this journey.
Your best pal...
confidant, Paul.
... escape from
Concord Park Institution
in Fresno has left two dead
and one injured.
Authorities tell us
that Paul Duerson
and Penelope Pascal
are unarmed
and should be considered
extremely dangerous.
- I won't be long.
- But, Dad,
- I don't think...
- Everything's fine.
Stay here with Aunt Eleanor
and be nice. Okay?
- I'm always nice.
- Um- hmm.
- Be careful.
- I'm always careful.
I love you.
You got the trunk
and the clothes!
Yeah.
See?!
I knew you could do it!
Ah.
Is that what I think it is?
It finally came.
You wanna go to McDonald's?
Hey, Paul.
There's a woman in the car.
That's Penny.
Bless you.
She's my PA.
What's a PA?
A personal assistant.
She helps Sofia and I
with our schedules
because we're both so busy.
I help with tasks.
To organize holidays
and gatekeep from unwanted...
... uh...
Kli... Kli... Klingons?
- Yes, Paul?
- Clingers-on.
Klingons are something...
totally different.
Hey... hey, Paul.
Maybe I could be your PA.
You know, JH,
it's best not to go into
business with your friends.
Hey, I thought you went home.
What, uh... what happened?
Let's get you inside.
Bell?
Paul Duerson escaped
from Concord Park two hours ago.
Huh.
Who the fuck
is this Paul Duerson?
What happens to your eye?
I lost it.
In a sword fight.
No.
He had a worm. A parasite.
It's not funny.
It's a little funny.
All right, Penny.
You're up first,
then we'll drop you, JH.
Can I help you?
Yes. Hello, mister.
My car is... is broke.
Can... can I use your telephone?
Well, I'm pretty good with cars.
Why don't I take a look at it?
Now, where's that accent from?
- Bell, right?
- Yeah.
You mind if I use
your phone real quick?
I'm gonna call a cab.
Sure, but they'll take
forever to get here. It's late.
The guest bedroom
should be made up.
Oh, yeah.
We were messing around.
And I... can't find
my clothes now.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got you.
Had fun tonight?
Yeah, Sofia is crazy, man.
So, this guy, um...
Paul Duerson.
Yeah.
How bad he get you?
Ruptured spleen.
Should have bled out.
He called the cops on himself.
Yeah?
Wait, slow down.
Call the police. I'm coming.
What?
What's going on, man?
I never should have left
her.
Fuck!
Lock this behind me.
Lu's on First, huh?
So, that's what this is.
What the fuck.
Hey. Cute top.
Where'd you get that?
Hey, look, it's cool
if you wanna... go.
Oh.
- That's it then?
- Well, yeah.
'Cause Bell's here,
Waylon's out front.
Bell left.
Where'd he go?
Hello? Got a call!
Hello?
Uh, got a call.
Yes, there's a strange man here.
- Inside?
- Outside.
So, there's not a man
here-here, then?
- No.
Is that out of the ordinary?
- For there to be a man outside?
- No.
This seems to be
a fairly busy block.
People walk.
People stroll.
Ms... ?
The guy was creepy,
all right?
And it's late.
You think I'd call the cops
for no reason?
That him?
What?
Is that the man from outside?
I'm not a man.
You think
this is funny?
No. But, uh...
everything
seems to be okay now.
And I gotta get up early
for an audition, so...
An audition?
Musical.
It's a black box theater thing.
Okay. Look, if you really
want me to hang out here,
I can, uh, stay here
and keep you safe.
How about a cup of coffee?
Oh, we'd feel safer
if you protected us
from your car outside.
Bicycle.
What?
Okay.
Should we get started
on the new one?
Have you seen this movie?
Because it looks like a riot.
Something wrong?
No.
It looks like
something's wrong.
You worked so hard
on this puzzle and...
we're just...
just gonna clean it all up?
Well yeah,
that's how puzzles work.
Yeah, finished with that one.
Are you crying?
Nah.
Okay.
I'm a puzzle.
What?
You built me up
for a minute.
You made me...
feel nice and...
whole and comfortable, and...
now, you're finished with me?
I didn't say
we were finished.
Yeah, but we're finished.
I can tell.
Just... put me back in my box.
Oo-kay. Um...
Uh... okay.
Hello?
- Fuck.
This keeps happening.
They were supposed to
fix this shit weeks ago.
Who is "they"?
I don't know.
The... light people?
Okay. Where's your
circuit breaker?
I don't know.
You don't know where
your circuit breaker is?
Do you know where
the circuit breaker is?
This is your house.
Well...
I have... many houses,
and many circuit breakers.
What?
That was
such a Sofia thing to say.
Excuse me?
Talking about how many
circuit breakers you have
is a rich person thing to say.
You're rich,
so you can't talk.
Rich...
is a state of mind.
What does that mean?
Like this thing.
It was a gift from Liberace.
It's funny.
It's creepy.
And I didn't know
people gave out
these candle holders as gifts.
But I guess fancy clothing
designers do.
It's called a candelabra.
And Liberace was a pianist,
you're thinking of Versace.
Again, a very
Sofia thing to say.
Dammit.
Ah, fuck.
Come on.
Where are you going?
To find
your circuit breaker.
Is there a problem here?
Actually, you know what?
I don't care.
I'm not doing this with you.
Doing what?
Digging any
deeper with you.
Yeah. No shit.
It is a little weird, though.
For you to be so...
how you are.
Like a Black guy,
you mean?
Please. Come on.
You're nothing at all
what people say about you.
You're more of a...
I'm not like what
who says about me?
Whoever wrote that list
on your desk...
that's some real
Ice Queen shit
to have just fucking
lying around.
And, where do I fit in?
How are you ever going to
find anything real?
- Real?
- Yeah.
What is that even?
Who the fuck are you?
I'm very sorry
your feelings were hurt,
but I kind of have
other things to worry about.
The psycho who tried to kill me
is on the loose.
He tried to kill Bell.
You weren't even home.
He thought he was stabbing me.
He wanted me dead!
What are you still doing here?
I don't need you
to protect me.
Okay, yeah.
'Cause you have armed guards
and a security system
from the future, right?
- Yeah, great point!
- Okay.
- You're not needed at all.
- All right, I'm out.
Oh, my balls!
I enjoy this American hat.
Uh-uh. Open sesame.
Waylon will call you a cab.
Help me!
Yee- haw!
Hey man,
can you open the gate?
Waylon?
Ow! Shit!
Am I an idiot?
Coo- coo.
Hello?
Rhodes?
Hey, Ladybug.
Ooh! I missed you a lot.
A lot. A lot.
Mm.
I owe you an apology.
I am so sorry
for leaving, honey.
Get away from me.
I...
Baby, I...
Don't do...
I don't know
what I was thinking.
Mmm.
Hi.
Hey, wait a second.
Wait. I can explain, baby.
Ow!
Enough with the little oranges!
Ow! Those are hard!
Baby, wait a sec.
That is such bad luck, Sofia!
Get out of my
fucking house!!!
Sofia.
Get out of here!
I'm trying. I'm trying!
Did my dad ever tell
you about Paul Duerson?
Like, what happened to him?
I saw on MTV News
that his girlfriend collapsed
during a Sofia concert.
A stroke or something
during "Father May I."
Just, boom,
dead at The Forum.
You want to know
what's also messed up?
I'm in the "Father May I"
music video
and it's always
projected behind Sofia
when she performs it.
So, maybe Paul Duerson's
girlfriend saw my face
and just, like, died.
- Hey.
- Hey, Dad.
Everyone okay?
I think the officer
might have scared him off.
Eleanor made him
wait outside.
There was nobody out there.
Get dressed.
- Where we going?
- Police station.
He was supposed to be
keeping an eye out.
He was just there.
♪ I just got an
Invitation through the mails ♪
♪ "Your presence requested
This evening, it's formal ♪
♪ A top hat,
A white tie and tails" ♪
♪ Nothing now could take
The wind out of my sails ♪
♪ Because I'm invited
To step out this evening ♪
♪ With top hat,
White tie and tails ♪
♪ Oh, I... ♪
♪ Oh, I'm puttin'
On my top hat ♪
♪ Tyin' up my white tie
Brushin' off my tails ♪
♪ I'm steppin' out, my dear ♪
♪ To breathe an atmosphere
That simply reeks with class ♪
♪ And I trust that
You'll excuse my dust ♪
♪ When I step on the gas ♪
♪ For I'll be there
Puttin' down my top hat ♪
♪ Mussin' up my white tie ♪
♪ And dancin' in my tails ♪
The heck?
The fuck did my chain go?
Who the hell steals a chain
from a police officer's bike?
Unbelievable.
Fucking West Side...
Is that the cop's?
Get in the car
and lock the doors.
Dad?
May I have that gun, please?
His hand is cold.
Let go of her.
Take us to Sofia's house,
please.
Paul is waiting for us.
Do you work for him?
You should never go
into business with friends.
♪ Now I don't hardly know her ♪
♪ But I think
I could love her ♪
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
♪ Ah... ♪
♪ When she comes walking over ♪
♪ Now I've been
Waiting to show her ♪
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ Da-da, da-da, da-da ♪
♪ My, my, such a sweet thing ♪
♪ Da-da, da-da, da-da ♪
♪ I wanna do everything ♪
♪ What a beautiful feeling ♪
♪ Da-da, da-da, da-da ♪
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
♪ Over and over ♪
♪ Da-da, da-da, da-da ♪
I killed someone.
Ow. Ow!
Hello, Clarice.
We've got a long,
long night ahead of us.
Listen. I know
you're super upset.
I know you're upset
that I left you.
But I really needed some time
to focus on me
before I could focus on us.
But now, I'm ready
to be yours forever.
And I mean... forever.
- Paul...
- And ever.
And ever, and ever,
and ever, and ever.
- Paul.
- And ever, and ever.
Call me Paul.
Paul.
I love it
when you call me by my name.
Okay. Um... listen.
You're confused. All right?
You're in the middle
of a psychotic...
um...
They told me
what happened to you.
At my show,
and I am so sorry.
Nobody should have
to go through that.
Okay?
But this is not the answer.
You're mad about the venue...
- Oh, my God. The venue?
- aren't you?
The Cassowary Tabernacle?
What?
The church
we're getting married at?
It's important to me.
We're getting married?
- Of course.
- Oh, God.
What, are you having
second thoughts?
Look, this snuck up on us,
and it's totally normal
to have feelings like this.
But I mean,
you knew all of this.
- Um...
- Are you feeling okay?
Um...
Okay, well, uh...
You gonna let me out then?
Of course.
Yeah, now?
Show you around the house.
Show you the Jacuzzi.
You're hilarious, Sofia.
Like I don't know
where the Jacuzzi is.
I've been here like
a bazillion times.
Will you please just
take the bag off her head.
No.
Why are you doing this?
I'm not supposed to say.
Paul's a real great planner,
and he don't want me
to ruin anything.
So, you just do whatever
he tells you to?
Is that it?
He's the only person who ever
treated me like a person.
Well, he's gotten you
into a lot of trouble.
Let them go.
We'll sort it out.
Pull over here.
Get out.
Find the nearest house.
Call the police.
Not them.
You.
Turn this song up.
Drive off and I'll kill him.
It's okay.
Where's he taking him?
- He'll be okay.
- ♪ ... reach a solution ♪
♪ I will end up
Lost in confusion ♪
♪ I don't care
If you really care ♪
♪ As long as you don't go ♪
♪ So I cry and I pray
And I beg ♪
Don't do this.
I'm sorry.
♪ Fool me fool me ♪
♪ Go on and fool me ♪
♪ Love me, love me
Pretend that you love me ♪
♪ Leave me, leave me
Just say that you need me ♪
♪ So I cry ♪
♪ And I beg for you to ♪
♪ Love me love me
Say that you love me ♪
- You can take the bag off now.
- ♪ Leave me, leave me ♪
♪ Just say that you need me ♪
♪ I can't care 'bout
Anything but you ♪
I have a surprise
for you.
Don't move a muscle.
Penny.
This is Penny.
She's a big fan of yours.
We met on the inside.
It was totally platonic.
She's great.
She's from Nice en France.
Spelled like "nice."
Nice.
Ha! Hilarious, Sofia. Truly.
Truly. Uh, uh...
Penny plays the piano
and sings, just like you.
Oh... mon dieu.
We could be a... a duet.
See? Friends already!
Look at that. Perfect!
Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
♪ Something in the way
You love me ♪
♪ Won't let me be ♪
♪ I don't want to be
Your prisoner ♪
♪ So baby
Won't you set me free? ♪
♪ Stop playin' with my heart
Finish what you start ♪
♪ When you make my love
Come down ♪
♪ If you want me let me know
Baby let it show ♪
♪ Come on now
Don't fool around ♪
♪ Something in your eyes ♪
♪ Is makin' such a fool of me ♪
♪ When you hold me in your arms
You love me ♪
♪ 'Til I just can't see ♪
♪ Just... ♪
♪ Try to understand ♪
♪ I've given all I can ♪
♪ 'Cause you got
The best of me ♪
♪ Borderline ♪
♪ Feels like I'm
Goin' to lose my mind ♪
♪ You just keep on pushin'
My love ♪
♪ Over the borderline ♪
You made it!
Whoo!
Welcome to the cocktail hour,
where drinks and hors d'oeuvres
will be served
before the shuttle
takes us to the church.
JH, put the gun away.
What kind of way is that
to treat our guests?
Our guests!
Oh!
How do I look?
Hi, Abby.
Uh, kids. Okay.
Come on.
Don't be scared.
Please remember
to sign the guest book.
It's nice.
Huh?
I am sorry, I borrowed some...
some clothes from your closet.
But it fits, no? It's good.
I am very excitement
for tonight.
Yes.
Um... Paul told me
you are in love.
I know this is not truth.
I know. But, you know,
as... as they say, um...
Uh...
Paul... Paul's elevator
does not reach the top floor.
You know? Americans!
I've never heard
that expression before.
Hmm.
But is... is this...
this is why I like Paul.
You know? He entertains me.
Watching him is like
watching a good movie.
So, he tells me,
he is to marry Sofia.
But...
he needs my help.
I think,
"Oui, merci, s'il vous plaît.
I would like to be
in this movie very much."
Coo-coo.
This yours. Take it.
It's nice, huh?
You know, you...
you have a wonderful, um...
skin and body. You have...
a great body.
Uh-huh.
Yes.
- Thanks.
- But...
uh, with honesty, I... I thought
you would be more beautiful.
Yes, is...
is a big disappointment for me.
All right. Well...
why don't you get my makeup?
Um-hmm.
Yeah, it's in my bathroom,
left of the sink.
Oh, um... and this...
will fix your face?
Yes, it will fix my face.
Okay. Okay.
Ah-ah...
Sofia.
Okay. Be back soon.
Fuck!
Oh, my god! Oh, my god!
Uh... okay.
May I offer you
a glass of champagne?
I'm kidding.
Of course you can't drink.
Evil, right?
You keep calling me.
I do.
Why?
Well, we wanted you
to be our flower girl.
JH picked out the dress.
What's that?
Huh. Would you?
Leaky pipes, I guess.
Paul?
Whew. Yes, flower girl?
Is someone in the trunk?
Please help me.
I'm in here. Hello?
Yes, flower girl.
Can we let him out?
Well... we were supposed to
wait until later,
but, uh... sure, why not?
Get to it.
Help me.
Pastor Lutzner.
Paul?
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is Pastor Tim Lutzner
of the Cassowary Tabernacle.
Please help yourself to
champagne and first aid.
You put a priest
in a box?
No, I put a pastor in a box.
We're Protestant.
Wake up, wake up,
wake up, wake up.
Hmm. Oh, thank god. Okay.
Hi.
Sorry I left you.
I'm sorry I hit you
in the face with a guitar.
Was it on purpose?
No.
Guy thinks
he's marrying you tonight.
I know. He bought me
a wedding dress.
It's blue.
It's fucked up.
I know.
Jesus.
Let go, you crazy bitch!
Duet, please.
What?
No.
Du...
...et.
I didn't even write this song.
I know.
'Cause this song is good.
- Come on.
- All right.
Yeah. Yeah.
♪ There were nights ♪
♪ When the wind was so cold ♪
♪ That my body froze in bed ♪
♪ If I just listened to it
Right outside the window ♪
♪ There were days when
The sun was so cruel ♪
♪ All the tears
turned to dust ♪
♪ And I just knew my eyes
Were drying up forever ♪
♪ I finished crying
In the instant that you left ♪
♪ And I can't remember
Where or when or how ♪
♪ And I banished every memory
You and I had ever made... ♪
♪ But when you touch me
Like this ♪
♪ And you hold me like that ♪
♪ I just have to admit ♪
♪ That it's all
Coming back to me ♪
♪ When I touch you like this ♪
♪ And I hold you like that ♪
♪ It's so hard to believe ♪
♪ That it's all
Coming back to me ♪
♪ There were moments of gold ♪
♪ And there were
Flashes of light ♪
♪ There were things
I'd never do again ♪
♪ But then they
Always seemed right ♪
♪ There were nights
Of endless pleasure ♪
♪ It was more than
Any laws allow... ♪
♪ Baby! Baby!
If I kiss you like this ♪
♪ And if you whisper
Like that... ♪
You are flat!
Fuck! What the fuck
is wrong with you?!
Stop!
Oh! Oh, no. Are you okay?
Do it!
Sofia doesn't
light people on fire.
Fuck.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Come on.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
God. Bless. You!
Yes!
Come on! Light me on fire!
Come on, Sofia!
Oh, fuck.
Wh... what could they
be doing up there?
Pas... Pastor Lutzner,
do you have any... ?
- Paul?
- Yes?
What are you trying
to achieve here?
Just a partnership
based on mutual admiration
and respect.
It's not real.
You see that, don't you?
None of it is real.
Paul?
She's probably just
figuring out her dress.
Last-minute dress alterations.
Yeah, I'm sure it's just
last- minute kinks
with the dress, right?
Girls will be girls,
Pastor Lutzner.
You might not know about that,
but girls will be girls.
Should... should I
go check on them?
No. No, no.
I'll go. I'll go. It's fine.
Saw a little girl here
when I snuck in.
Black girl. Ten or eleven.
Okay, okay. Um...
Fuck.
You stay here.
I'll be right back.
I'll be right back. Okay.
Honey?
Everything okay in here?
You re...
Oh my god, I'm so sorry.
You're just the most beautiful
thing I've ever seen.
Why aren't you ready?
And where's Penny?
Is there something wrong
with the dress?
I'm...
I so... understand.
This is really scary.
But I adore you, Ladybug.
From your head
all the way down to your toes.
Abby! Abby!
Hey!
You're supposed to be
getting ready.
Who are you?
How awesome is this, huh?
Rajput warriors
are gifted this
on their wedding day.
It's sharp on both sides.
To protect you
from your enemies...
and your friends...
whoever came in the way
of your happiness.
But I won't let anyone...
come in the way
of our happiness.
Yo, what the fuck
are you talking about?
I love you.
Are you okay?
You're okay.
Where's your dad?
You dead?
Hello?
Are you okay?
Taylor?
Kaylor.
What happened to your head?
We should really
get you to a hospital.
I need a car.
You have a Porsche?
It's so fast.
Guess I'm walking.
"Welcome to
Paul and Sofia wedding."
Father Tim Lutzner. Tim.....
Lutzner. Motherfucker!
♪ Sweet baby Jesus ♪
♪ Won't you come ♪
♪ See me get married ♪
♪ To my love ♪
♪ Sweet baby Jesus ♪
♪ I see you watchin' ♪
♪ From above ♪
♪ Sweet baby Jesus... ♪
Let's get all units to
Cassowary Tabernacle.
I hate the fucking Hills.
♪ ... I see you watching ♪
♪ Sweet Jesus... ♪
Okay. Everybody ready?
Great. Let's do it.
Flower girl, you look great.
What are you doing?
What?
Please take a seat.
It's about to start.
Ma'am, today's not about you.
Thank you.
Shouldn't you be up there?
I don't know.
Uh, Paul?
Uh, JH?
Ar... aren't you marrying Sofia?
Of course.
Uh, Sofia is...
JH...
you've been one hell
of a best man.
I got it from here.
Okay? Your job's done.
Flower girl, get back there,
please.
Get some hustle. Hustle.
Okay, great.
Hit it, JH.
Throw the... throw the flowers.
Dad!
Don't upset him.
He gets violent
when he's confused.
I'm in a wedding dress, man.
I think he's pretty
fucking confused.
Thank you.
For your kindness
and graciousness.
I'll treat her right.
And I'm sorry
my hands are so sweaty.
Hey, you mind
if I greet the guests?
Oh, of course. Just, um...
would you sit on my side?
It's empty.
It's great to see you.
Thanks for coming.
Everything's gonna be okay.
The big one has a gun.
I know. He shot me
in the head with it.
Dearly beloved,
we are gathered here today
to join Paul Duerson
and this...
person...
in holy matrimony.
Uh, hey, Paul?
Down, JH.
That's not Sofia.
What are you talking about?
He's a man.
And he's Black.
And he don't look
nothing like her.
There's Sofia.
Don't listen to him.
Baby, it's me. I'm here.
I'm Sofia.
Pastor Lutzner...
you can continue.
If anyone present believes
these two persons should not
be joined in holy matrimony,
speak now or forever
hold their peace.
I do. I... I... object.
No. No. You don't have to.
And it's my fault
we're all here.
So, I should be the one
up there with you.
Not him, Paul.
You do look beautiful,
by the way.
Thank you.
You know, being with me is
not all it's cracked up to be.
But hey, you're the only person
who's ever wanted to marry me.
So fuck it, let's do it.
Let's get married.
- Ma'am?
- Yeah?
I told you
to sit down and be quiet.
Today is not about you.
Please?
For the rest of us?
Thank you.
I'm so sorry.
You can skip ahead
to the good stuff. We're ready.
The good stuff?
Yeah. You know,
the kissing.
Um, all right.
Do you, Paul, take...
Your name?
Sofia.
Do you, Paul,
take Sofia to be
your lawfully-wedded wife?
I do.
And do you, Sofia,
take Paul
to be your
lawfully-wedded husband?
I do.
Well... in the presence
of family and friends,
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Hey, shouldn't we do something?
Let him have it.
It's all he wanted.
♪ Sweet baby Jesus ♪
♪ I'm alive ♪
♪ I'm awake ♪
♪ Dear Jesus above ♪
♪ I see you watchin' ♪
♪ Sweet Jesus ♪
♪ From a tower up above ♪
♪ Sweet baby Jesus ♪
♪ I'm alive ♪
No!
Sofia...
I'm sorry.
It's over, Paul.
I really love it
when you call me by name.
Are you okay?
Don't move!
- Let her go.
- Hey, Paul.
I got myself
in a hostage situation.
Please let her go.
You! Dr... drop that knife.
Do it.
Just take it easy.
Now kick it over here.
Just... let her go
and you guys can leave, okay?
You don't need her.
I might.
For... for leverage.
You don't want this
on your conscience.
I don't think
I got one of those.
Weddings are supposed to be fun!
Oh my God.
Jesus Christ.
I don't think
I meant to do that.
I don't think... I don't think
What the fuck?
♪ ...let us rejoice
and let us sing and dance ♪
♪ And ring in the new ♪
♪ Hail, Atlantis... ♪
♪ Way down below the ocean ♪
♪ Where I wanna be ♪
♪ She may be ♪
♪ Way down below the ocean ♪
♪ Where I wanna be ♪
♪ She may be ♪
♪ Way down below the ocean ♪
♪ Where I wanna be ♪
♪ She may be... ♪
♪ Way down below the ocean ♪
♪ Where I wanna be ♪
♪ She may be... ♪
♪ Way down below the ocean ♪
- ♪ Where I wanna be ♪
- ♪ She may be... ♪
So, hotshot.
Should we give this thing a try?
It'll never work out.
Why not?
I'm a married man.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, I want you to know
that you were right.
I can't be doing this anymore.
It's too dangerous.
You think?
What are you
going to do for work?
Something that gets me
home to you in one piece.
You mean something
that doesn't get you stabbed
or shot in the head?
Or me covered in blood?
Yeah.
Dad, this is
freaking disgusting.
You know, I've never been
in a limousine before.
Drop us off at the Hilton where
we have the penthouse suite.
And in the morning... Maui.
What a night.
♪ One night ♪
♪ I had a thought ♪
♪ What if we ordered
Anything we want ♪
♪ We quit our jobs
We went outside ♪
♪ No one could tell us
How to live our lives ♪
♪ One night, I took a drug ♪
♪ I gave three hundred
Uninvited hugs ♪
♪ You went to bed
I hit the floor ♪
♪ I don't think that we should
Get together anymore ♪
♪ One night
Came and went ♪
♪ Spent lots of money,
It was money well spent ♪
♪ I took on some credit card,
Credit card debt ♪
♪ On a night that didn't
Mean nothing ♪
♪ A night I'll
probably forget ♪
♪ One night,
I had a feeling ♪
♪ Bust through a wall
Cut through the ceiling ♪
♪ 27 Club and I'm still
Fucking breathing ♪
♪ I'm hyperventilating in
A building full of people ♪
♪ It's beginning
To feel like I've ♪
♪ Been training my whole life
For nothing ♪
♪ I've been meaning to
Tell you something ♪
♪ You gotta lean into life
Just a little ♪
♪ I think I'm breaking
My own heart ♪
♪ I think I'm making
My own self sick ♪
♪ At the thought
Of getting sick ♪
♪ I don't leave any more ♪
♪ Did I leave
My keys in the door? ♪
♪ It was so peaceful before ♪
♪ Come on buddy, you gotta
Lean into life a bit ♪
♪ You gotta callus up
Them hands ♪
♪ And get some dirt
Under them fingertips ♪
♪ I, ah, don't think it's skin
And papier-mâché ornaments ♪
♪ Another Christmas Eve
And you're still bumming out ♪
♪ About the same shit ♪
♪ Come on my friend ♪
♪ yeah You're really
going through it ♪
♪ You got all this free time, ♪
♪ No fucking idea
What to do with it ♪
♪ Sounds an awful lot to me ♪
♪ Like you like talking
About your bootstraps ♪
♪ Go to hell, I am the devil ♪
♪ Trying to claw
My way to heaven ♪
♪ I am regretful
We had our weekend ♪
♪ Filled with cocaine
And Essentia ♪
♪ It was fun and now
I can't really remember ♪
♪ And yeah we wonder why
We can't reach our potential ♪
♪ I am regretful
Yeah my head is in the gutter ♪
♪ Do we really need to sin
To love each other ♪
♪ Another psycho I'll get
Fucked up then recover ♪
♪ I just want to be
A better older brother ♪
♪ My head is in the gutter ♪
♪ It's beginning to
Feel like I've ♪
♪ Been training my whole life
For nothing ♪
♪ I've been meaning to
Tell you something ♪
♪ You gotta lean into life,
Just a little ♪
♪ I think I'm breaking
My own heart ♪
♪ I think I'm making
My own self sick ♪
♪ At the thought
Of getting sick ♪
♪ I don't leave any more ♪
♪ Did I leave my keys
In the door? ♪
♪ It was so peaceful before ♪